# TODO deal with extended attributes
# TODO implement globbing
# TODO implement STDIN reading
# TODO deal with identifiers (Name, Code) by limiting the characters (specific "charset"?)
# TODO deal with RTF (in long strings)
# IDEA deal with binary format
# IDEA replace scripts (GTL, vbscript...) in extensions, with valid scripts
# IDEA replace numeric values
# IDEA replace binary blobs (images...)
# IDEA use parameter to specific more attributes to replace
# IDEA replace long text with excerpts from a pre-defined text
# IDEA add option to disable charset-matching when replacing values
# IDEA add option to pass "valid chars" expression
